How we doing?
>> It's been a little while. Um,
>> I guess I'll open it up for questions.
Uh, actually, first and foremost, um, I
wanted to, uh, congratulate Luke
Keequley on, uh, the Hall of Fame. Uh,
couldn't go to a more deserving guy. um
the competitor um you know the
instincts, the playmaking ability, and
then the person he is off the field. It
couldn't have happened to a better
person. So really happy for Luke.
>> I guess that's a perfect way to seg.
Yeah, you know, I think um you know, in
terms of free agency in the draft, um I
think that's a position that we'll, you
know, try to attack. Um you know, we're
looking for guys that that are that are
leaders, that are playmakers,
um and that are culture fits for us. So,
we're excited about attacking that and
putting the work in. Dan, speaking of
like a segue NFL,
how do you speak to that position
value?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think the linebacker
position super valuable. That's the guy
that's standing in front of your huddle
every single play. He's the D line's
looking at him, the DBs are looking at
him. Um, and they're they're looking at
him for leadership. So, I think that
position right there is super valuable
and and it's one that, you know, I think
everybody should should really value
high.
>> How does how is impacting the big round
draft picks and do you see it as a
positive or a potential negative?
>> Um, you know, the I don't really look at
the NIL as a bad thing. Um, you know, I
think the the NIL is actually somewhat
of a good thing because it gives us a
little bit of a snapshot of a guy, what
he's like with money. Um, so from my
perspective, it's it's good to kind of
see like what did he do with this money?
Um, you know, did he spend it
recklessly? Did he go out and, you know,
get in trouble with it? So, it tells you
a lot about somebody. So, if anything, I
think it's really valuable for us.
Um, I I don't think anything's going to
be off the table. Um, we'll, you know,
we'll explore that. You know, we'll talk
to his agent. Um, but I wouldn't say
anything's upcoming, but we'll
definitely stay in that and we'll see
where that goes.
>> Um, know a lot about them. Uh,
obviously, you know, when guys get cut,
I watch every guy that that gets cut. So
do the pro scouts. They do a great job
as well. So, uh, still playing at a
really good level. Uh, has had a lot of
sack production throughout his career.
Just a really good player and, um, you
know, that's something that we'll we'll
stay in and we'll explore.
>> As far as the draft availability, the
numbers continue to fall when it comes
to underassman.
Do you see it as as a positive or a
negative? I mean, with each draft that
you may have fewer underassman because
they're staying
>> Yeah, I mean that's one of the
negatives. You know, there's some guys
this year that I watched that I wish
would have came out and but there's also
some that came out. So, um I think you
know, our job is to just evaluate who's
available and and go from there. So, uh,
you know, we're excited about this draft
class and, you know, there's some really
good underassman. There's some good, you
know, seniors. So, um, I don't I don't
really think it matters too much. We
just got we just got to evaluate who's
at our disposal.
>> Yeah.
>> How did that go? What's the timeline?
>> Uh, first of all, the surgery surgery
went really well. Uh Icky is doing
really good. He's recovering, feeling
good. I just talked to him the other
day. So he's in good spirits. Uh
unfortunate what happened. Obviously
timelinewise I don't really have a
timeline. You know, we'll see how it
progresses. We'll see how it goes. And
but so far it's looking good and you
know, as far as a timeline, I don't have
that right now. Um, in terms of it of it
impacting the draft, free agency, you
know, offensive line is is a position
that we're always going to be looking
at, always trying to upgrade and have as
much depth as possible there. Um, so
we're just, you know, going to attack
that like we usually do.
>> Yeah.
I mean, I don't I don't know that. I
think our trainers have done a really
good job with him so far. He is making
progress. I don't have a timeline on it.
I really don't. But, you know, I'm
optimistic that is going to put the work
in and and he'll be ready, you know,
when that time comes.
You got four guys.
>> I mean, we're talking to all of our free
agents and that includes the offensive
line. We're going to stay in contact
with the agents and, you know, we'll see
where it goes. But, you know, again,
we're going to try to create as much
depth and competition as possible there.
And you know that's with every position
on the roster.
>> Dan, with that said though, you have a
top three like payroll line and D line.
How do you kind of share the wealth with
other positions this offseason knowing
that you have center open and left
tackle potentially open?
>> Yeah. And you know, I think that's a
little bit by design, too. You know,
when I took took over this job, the
number one thing I wanted to do is make
us strong on both sides of the ball. And
you know that's never going to change as
long as I'm the GM here. So um what was
the second part of your question?
>> Just how do how do you kind of spread
the wealth out you know in free agency
spending [snorts] wise when you have
such a high pay for both?
>> Yeah. I mean we we have cap room. You
know there's different different ways to
create more cap room if we if we see
fit. Um, so we're just going to continue
to just add good players to our roster,
great players to our roster, and you
know, no matter what position it is,
we're just going to, you know, try to
make this roster as strong and as
competitive as as it can be.
>> What kind of trust do you have?
>> Got a lot of trust in them. I think Chu
Chuba has proved that he can be a number
one back. he can carry the load, which
he has done. Uh, you know, in terms of
Jonathan Brooks coming back, we're
excited about that. His rehab, you know,
he's doing a great job with that, making
a lot of progress. So, we feel good
about him. We're happy for him. We're
optimistic for him. And then Trevor ETN,
who we drafted last year. We're really
excited about him. Uh, we think he's got
a bright future. Uh, and I think he's
going to be one of those rising stars in
this in this league. So, we feel good
about the room, but again, that doesn't
mean we won't add to that room. Um,
whether in free agency, resigning
people, uh, or in the draft. So, we're
just going to attack every position.
>> Um, I wouldn't say he exceeded my
expectations. He was everything that we
thought he was going to be. Uh, just a
big talented receiver that can run the
route tree. Uh he's got great hands.
He's got run after catch. So he
definitely was everything we thought he
was. And you know, just like everybody,
he's he's going to improve. He's going
to get better the more experience he
gets in our scheme, uh the more
continuity he creates with Bryce. So
he's just going to keep getting better
and better. And I think the future is
bright for him and for our team.
>> Who's that?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, you know, I think uh a veteran,
obviously, you bring a veteran in uh
who's played a lot of football, that's
obviously going to help your team. But
we're really excited about our young
guys, you know, uh Scorton and
Princeley, we drafted them for a reason.
We drafted them high for a reason. We
think they're super talented guys that
can be impact players in this league and
they're going to keep developing.
They're going to keep getting better and
uh again I think the future's really
really bright for for those two guys and
they're going to help us out a lot.
>> Josh
or something. How do you settle?
>> Um no you know just helping a friend
out. You know, I think, you know, John
asked me about him and obviously I gave
him a really good recommendation. Uh
Mike's a great guy, great coach, and
just really happy for them.
team players psychologically, not just
physically in the rehab process.
>> Yeah, I think that's a great question.
Um, first first off, you know,
condolences go out to him and his and
his family, uh, friends, loved ones. Uh,
it's just super tragic and me being a
former player, um, you know, I'm always
trying to help our players out and guide
them. I know what they're going through
on a day-to-day basis. Um, I went
through that myself. I went through a
lot of injuries as a player. It's not
easy. Um, you feel alone at times. You
feel like, you know, you feel like
people kind of abandon you a little bit.
Um, but at the same time, you know,
that's the advantage I have being the GM
of the Panthers to where I can help
these guys out. I understand what
they're going through. I'm here for
them. And then obviously, there's always
going to be resources. You know, we have
a great psychologist on our staff um,
who players can talk to at any time. and
we're just always here to support them.
They know we're here for them and
that'll never change.
>> What's that?
>> What would you say about Rico?
>> Yeah, I think with Rico, um, obviously I
love Rico. Great guy, great player, had
a great year for us this year. Um, I
think, you know, in terms of he's earned
the ability to go out there and see
what's out there for him. there's always
the potential that he could come back.
Um the doors open for that and you know
we'll see what happens.
>> I don't think so. You know I think you
know it's a case by case basis thing.
You know I think Javvante is separate
from Rico. Um it's a pretty deep free
agent running back class. Um so we'll
we'll see what happens. And you know
again I wish the best for Rico. you
know, if he does go out and find
something, find a big deal. Um, but
there is always that potential, maybe we
could bring him back.
>> Anything else?
>> How folks [snorts]
Yeah, I don't think I don't think you
can have too many really good pass
rushers. So, you know, the combination
of free agency, the combination of
draft. There's some good players in both
that we're excited about. So, we'll see
how it shakes out. Uh we're obviously
evaluating them. We're putting the work
in and you know, we'll see what happens.
>> Is there a concept of
want to bring.
>> Yeah, I mean there's the potential for
that. Um, obviously I don't have a
crystal ball and you know, you never
know who you're going to sign um or who
may want to come here, but all options
are on the table right now. Um, I think
it's a good point to to bring a vet in.
Um, that can never hurt, but at the same
time, we're, you know, you can't go
chase chase guys either. And then
finally, can you give us an update on
Pat?
>> Yeah, he's doing good. Uh, he's fully
cleared. He'll be ready to go next year.
And yeah, he's doing great. He put he
did a great job in rehab, putting the
work in and getting himself back and he
looks great and we're excited to get him
back.
>> Um, you know, I think like the first
time you do it, everything's new, right?
So, everybody's in your face at the
podium. it's it's kind of overwhelming a
little bit. Um, so I think like the
longer you're in it, the more you get
used to it, the more you get
comfortable. Um, and you start, you
know, just kind of settling into the
position. So, yeah, I think, you know,
I'm I'm always going to be trying to
learn, always trying to get better with
everything I do with processes, with
evaluations, just always trying to get
better, always trying to help my staff
and, you know, and them doing to me
likewise. So, uh, just kind of being
that servant leader.
>> Dan, uh, last year you basically had
some spot during training camp.
>> Yeah.
>> There's some confusion there. Have you
talked to the league at all about
89?
>> Yeah. Yeah, actually did bring that up.
Um, you know, we're still working
through all that type of stuff, but that
is something I bought up having 89 guys
when you know, you know, you're going to
put a guy down on IR. Um, so I think,
you know, from a player safety and, you
know, just keeping guys healthy, I think
it would be a good idea to definitely
change that.
>> Do you think you'll propose that
potentially as a change?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I think it's definitely the
potential of that.
last year.
[snorts]
>> Yeah, I think it's a really good group
of edge rushers, you know, first round,
second round, third round. I think it's
a pretty deep edge class that we're
excited about. And again, you know, if
the possibility of one of those guys is
there at our picks, um, we'll definitely
consider it. But again, we're always
going to draft best available players.
So, if that's the best available player,
then so be it.
>> Thanks, Dan. [music]
[music]
>> [music]